Tufts Journal UP054
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Tufts Journal, 1980 -- 2006; UP054.001; 2.65 Linear Feet; 10 Volumes
  - Tufts Journal, October, 1988; UP054.001.008.00022 (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Alumni/ae] Overseas alums a powerful resource for Tufts; Academic Awards 1988-89. Angela Lagasse A 92 and Craig Quintero A 92 receive National Hispanic Scholarship Award. [Alani, Salim M.] Director in Internal Audit Dept. presented seminar on "Auditing Veterinary Hospitals".
  - Tufts Journal, November, 1988; UP054.001.008.00023 (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Albert, Dick] Meteorologist for WCVB-TV hosts a discussion at Fletcher symposium. [American Association of Equine Practioners] 2-minutes, 2 finger racehorse
  - Tufts Journal, December, 1988; UP054.001.008.00024 (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room.
  - Tufts Journal, 1989 February; UP054.000273 (Box 8)
    10, 6
  - Tufts Journal, 1989 April; UP054.001.008.00025 (Box 8)
  - Tufts Journal, May, 1989; UP054.001.008.00026 (Box 8)
  - Tufts Journal, September, 1989; UP054.001.008.00027 (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Dr. Ross Abrams [New England Medical Center]. New England Medical Center radiation department joins national group.; W. Steven Adair grant recipient p. 8. [Allergies] Treatments. Juan Alonso (faculty) Author of The Chipped Wall.
  - Tufts Journal, November, 1989; UP054.001.008.00028 (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Adomeit, Hannes] East Germany. pp. 1, 2.
  - Tufts Journal, December, 1989; UP054.001.008.00029 (Box 8)
  - Tufts Journal, February, 1990; UP054.001.008.00030 (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [American association for the advancement of Science] Professors address annual meeting; W. Steven Adair grant received. p. 8. David F. Albertini is Speaker at Workshop in Molecular Biology.
  - Tufts Journal, March, 1990; UP054.001.008.00031 (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Katrina Altmaier [V1986] Eqine Symposium; [Afsar, Mohammed] Grant recipient, p. 10.; Aidekman Arts Center [1989-90]. Construction update.; [AIDS] Marketing new drugs, p. 11.
  - Tufts Journal, May, 1990; UP054.001.008.00032 (Box 8)
  - Tufts Journal, September, 1990; UP054.001.008.00033 (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. NEASC [Northeast Association of Schools and Colleges] will reevaluate p. 3. Acting Dean of Faculty of Arts, Sciences and Technology (1990). Feinleib, MaryElla; [Administration] Budget process, p. 1, 4; Mary Ella Feinleib, Acting Dean, p. 1, 4.; [AIDS] Red tape thwarts, pp. 1, 3.
  - Tufts Journal, October, 1990; UP054.001.008.00034 (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. A. Alcivar (Former postdoctoral research assoc.) Presented paper in Knoxville, TN; Katrina Altmaier [vetrinary school] gave update on vaccine for Potomac horse fever
  - Tufts Journal, November, 1990; UP054.001.008.00035 (Box 8)
  - Tufts Journal, December, 1990; UP054.001.008.00036 (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Accreditation Committee] Committees picked and ready to start working. p. 2. Paul Ackerman. Named development records supervisor.; [Admissions 1990] Minority applicants. [Alumni 1990] Dental School alum elected first woman president of American Dental Association, p. 11. [Alumni 1990] Liberal arts is good preparation for career, p. 3.
  - Tufts Journal, February, 1991; UP054.001.008.00037 (Box 8)
  - Tufts Journal, March, 1991; UP054.001.008.00038 (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Shirley F. Aidekman. Elected charter member of trustees.
  - Tufts Journal, April, 1991; UP054.001.008.00039 (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Missing
  - Tufts Journal, May, 1991; UP054.001.008.00040 (Box 8)
  - Tufts Journal, September, 1991; UP054.001.008.00041 (Box 8)
  - Tufts Journal, October, 1991; UP054.001.008.00042 (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Adomeit, Hannes] Director of new Soviet and Central European Program at Fletcher. p. 9. Kenneth Aidekman [A75]. Gary Aidekman [A73]. Shirley and Alex Aidekman Arts Center.
  - Tufts Journal, November, 1991; UP054.001.008.00043 (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Admissions 1991-92] Admissions holds information sessions in city churches; [Afsar, Mohammed] Tufts engineer works fusion reaction, p. 3.
  - Tufts Journal, December, 1991; UP054.001.008.00044 (Box 8)
  - Tufts Journal, February, 1992; UP054.001.008.00045 (Box 8)
  - Tufts Journal, April, 1992; UP054.001.008.00047 (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Alumni association] Distinguished service awards presented to six alums; [Adel H. Aba-Moustafa] hosted Shuaib A. Shuail President of Kuwait Univ. p. 10. Abdul Abumoustafa. Visited King Abdulaziz University in Saudi Arabia. Ana Achucarro. Awarded grant. AIDS Quilt in Cousens Gym [photo].
  - Tufts Journal, May, 1992; UP054.001.008.00048 (Box 8)
  - Tufts Journal, September, 1992; UP054.001.008.00049 (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Admissions, Office of] "How I Spent My Summer Vacation" pp. 2, 15; [Alumni association] Alum named secretary of the corporation for Tufts
  - Tufts Journal, October, 1992; UP054.001.008.00050 (Box 8)
  - Tuts Journal, November, 1992; UP054.001.008.00051 (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. "Action and Altruism: The Ethics of Moral Courage." History's unsung heroes.; [Administration] A Celebration of Jean Mayer's Presidency. pp. 1, 4. David Albertini (Faculty) Gave presentation at UNC, seminar to EPA, chaired Grodon conference.
  - Tufts Journal, December, 1992; UP054.001.008.00052 (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Administration] Former tufts VP dies in Belmont. p. 2.
  - Tufts Journal, February, 1993; UP054.001.008.00053 (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Adel Abu-Moustafa. Negotiated Technical Contract with King Abdulaziz University.
  - Tufts Journal, March, 1993; UP054.001.008.00054 (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [American association for the advancement of science] Tufts at AAAS: 5 faculty members gave presentations; Co-winner, 1st prize for poster at National Head Injury Foundation symposium. no. 6 p. 8. Herbert Abrams. Visiting lecturer in ExCollege, retired as associative justice, to become counsel to law firm. Richard B. Miller Abrams [A76, F78]. Senior partner of law firm of Abrams, Roberts Klickstein and Levy; [Afrow, Jay] Appointed associate chief dentist at Fernald School, p. 8; [Afsar, Mohammed N.] Eureka-after 40 years: Prof. Afsar shows that theoretical physicists were right: wins award for paper, p. 8.
  - Tufts Journal, April, 1993; UP054.001.008.00055 (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Alumni relations] DiBiaggio to be inaugurated; [Alumni association] Distinguished service awards and Senior awards presented; [Admissions, Office of] April Open House for Class of '97. p. 2. Acacia Alcivar-Warren (Vet. faculty) Is equine speed inherited?.
  - Tufts Journal, May, 1993; UP054.001.008.00056 (Box 8)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Aditya, Shoma] It's not magic-it's chemistry. p. 19; [Afsar, Mohamed] Chariman of International Conference on Millimeter and submillimeter waves and applications, p. 15.
  - Tufts Journal, October, 1993; UP054.001.009.00001 (Box 9)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Ambulatory farm service, Life on the farm
  - Tufts Journal, November, 1993; UP054.001.009.00002 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Journal, December, 1993; UP054.001.009.00003 (Box 9)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Aymen Aboushala. [Abdulwahab Al-shuria] You can take advantage of aesthetic dentistry program; [Aesthetic Fellowship Program] You can take advantage of aesthetic dentistry program, p. 11.
  - Tufts Journal, February, 1994; UP054.001.009.00004 (Box 9)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Administration 1994] Feinlab, Nelson to resign; [Afrow, Jay] Guest speaker at annual meeting of Massachusetts Public Health and School Hygenists, p. 8. [Alcivar-Warren, Acacia] Genetics may quench Americans' insatiable appetite for shrimp.
  - Tufts Journal, March, 1994; UP054.001.009.00005 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Journal, April, 1994; UP054.001.009.00006 (Box 9)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Agaian, Sos] Visiting specialist in Elctrical engineering, p. 8. Dr. Albert Ahn. Spoke at annual ski meeting of the American animal hospital association.
  - Tufts Journal, May, 1994; UP054.001.009.00007 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Journal, September, 1994; UP054.001.009.00008 (Box 9)
    [Administration 1994-95] Oppurtunities for collaboration drive new Arts and Sciences administrators.
  - Tufts Journal, October, 1994; UP054.001.009.00009 (Box 9)
    [American association of medical colleges] Medical magazine wins top writing award; [AIDS] Why do AIDS patients suffer devestating weight loss?. [Alani, Salim M. (Director of Internal Audit)] Elected executive Vice-pres. of the New England chapter of the Information System Audit and control association.
  - Tufts Journal, November, 1994; UP054.001.009.00010 (Box 9)
    Aidekman Arts Center. Educating the artist.
  - Tufts Journal, December, 1994; UP054.001.009.00011 (Box 9)
    [Alpha Epsilon Pi] Faculty waits on you dinner [photoessay]; [African-American Center] Creating support network for Black students, p. 10; [Agbeli, Godwin] The world at Tufts:reception for International students and faculty, p. 6,7.
  - Tufts Journal, February, 1995; UP054.001.009.00012 (Box 9)
    Acoustical Society of America (1994/95). Can you hear it?
  - Tufts Journal, March, 1995; UP054.001.009.00013 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Journal, April, 1995; UP054.001.009.00014 (Box 9)
    Dr. Adel Abu-Moustafa. Faculty exchange prgram. Lester Adelman. Taught course in Saudi Arabia. [Alcohol and Health Education] Program emphasizes education and support. [Alliance to Save Student Aid] You need to fight for student aid,
  - Tufts Journal, May, 1995; UP054.001.009.00015 (Box 9)
    Aidekman Arts Center [1994/95]. "Reading the Image."; Ten students receive Tufts Senior Awards
  - Tufts Journal, September, 1995; UP054.001.009.00016 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Journal, October, 1995; UP054.001.009.00017 (Box 9)
    Henry David Abraham (former faculty). Medical Diagnosis in a Flicker. [Alani, Salim M.] Elected president of audit and control association.
  - Tufts Journal, November, 1995; UP054.001.009.00018 (Box 9)
    [Aidekman Arts Center, 1995-96] Neo-Dada at the Aidekman. [AIDS] Participants needed for HIV study.
  - Tufts Journal, December, 1995; UP054.001.009.00019 (Box 9)
    Othman S. Altwairgi cormack award winner; Dr. Adel Abu-moustafa. Reached an agreement to help university in Saudi Arabia.
  - Tufts Journal, February, 1996; UP054.001.009.00020 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Journal, March, 1996; UP054.001.009.00021 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Journal, April, 1996; UP054.001.009.00022 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Journal, May, 1996; UP054.001.009.00023 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Journal, September, 1996; UP054.001.009.00024 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Journal, October, 1996; UP054.001.009.00025 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Journal, November, 1996; UP054.001.009.00026 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Journal, December, 1996; UP054.001.009.00027 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Journal, February, 1997; UP054.001.009.00028 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Journal, March, 1997; UP054.001.009.00029 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Journal, April, 1997; UP054.001.009.00030 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Journal, May, 1997; UP054.001.009.00031 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Journal, September, 1997; UP054.001.009.00032 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Journal, October, 1997; UP054.001.009.00033 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Journal, November, 1997; UP054.001.009.00034 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Journal, December, 1997; UP054.001.009.00035 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Journal, February, 1998; UP054.001.009.00036 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Journal, March, 1998; UP054.001.009.00037 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Journal, April, 1998; UP054.001.009.00038 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Journal, May, 1998; UP054.001.009.00039 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Journal, September, 1998; UP054.001.009.00040 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Journal, October, 1998; UP054.001.009.00041 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Journal, November, 1998; UP054.001.009.00042 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Journal, December, 1998; UP054.001.009.00043 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Journal, February, 1999; UP054.001.009.00044 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Journal, March, 1999; UP054.001.009.00045 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Journal, April, 1999; UP054.001.009.00046 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Journal, May, 1999; UP054.001.009.00047 (Box 9)
  - Tufts Journal, September, 1999; UP054.001.010.00001 (Box 10)
  - Tufts Journal, October, 1999; UP054.001.010.00002 (Box 10)
  - Tufts Journal, November, 1999; UP054.001.010.00003 (Box 10)
  - Tufts Journal, December, 1999; UP054.001.010.00004 (Box 10)
  - Tufts Journal, February, 2000; UP054.001.010.00005 (Box 10)
  - Tufts Journal, March, 2000; UP054.001.010.00006 (Box 10)
  - Tufts Journal, April, 2000; UP054.001.010.00007 (Box 10)
  - Tufts Journal, May, 2000; UP054.001.010.00008 (Box 10)
  - Tufts Journal, September, 2000; UP054.001.010.00009 (Box 10)
  - Tufts Journal, October, 2000; UP054.001.010.00010 (Box 10)
  - Tufts Journal, November, 2000; UP054.001.010.00011 (Box 10)
  - Tufts Journal, December, 2000; UP054.001.010.00012 (Box 10)
  - Tufts Journal, February, 2001; UP054.001.010.00013 (Box 10)
  - Tufts Journal, March, 2001; UP054.001.010.00014 (Box 10)
  - Tufts Journal, November, 2003; UP054.001.011.00001 (Box 11)
    Volume, issue
    25, 3
  - Tufts Journal, December, 2003; UP054.001.011.00002 (Box 11)
    25, 4
  - Tufts Journal, February, 2004; UP054.001.011.00003 (Box 11)
    25, 5
  - Tufts Journal, March, 2004; UP054.001.011.00004 (Box 11)
    25, 6
  - Tufts Journal, April, 2004; UP054.001.011.00005 (Box 11)
    25, 7
  - Tufts Journal, May, 2004; UP054.001.011.00006 (Box 11)
    25, 8
  - Tufts Journal, September, 2004; UP054.001.011.00007 (Box 11)
    26, 1
  - Tufts Journal, October, 2004; UP054.001.011.00008 (Box 11)
    26, 2
  - Tufts Journal, November, 2004; UP054.001.011.00009 (Box 11)
    26, 3
  - Tufts Journal, December, 2004; UP054.001.011.00010 (Box 11)
    26, 4
  - Tufts Journal, February, 2005; UP054.001.011.00011 (Box 11)
    26, 5
  - Tufts Journal, March, 2005; UP054.001.011.00012 (Box 11)
    26, 6
  - Tufts Journal, April, 2005; UP054.001.011.00013 (Box 11)
    26, 7
  - Tufts Journal, May, 2005; UP054.001.011.00014 (Box 11)
    26, 8
  - Tufts Journal, September, 2005; UP054.001.011.00015 (Box 11)
    27, 1
  - Tufts Journal, October, 2005; UP054.001.011.00016 (Box 11)
    27, 2
  - Tufts Journal, November, 2005; UP054.001.011.00017 (Box 11)
    27, 3
  - Tufts Journal, December, 2005; UP054.001.011.00018 (Box 11)
    27, 4
  - Tufts Journal, Feb., 2006; UP054.001.011.00019 (Box 11)
    27, 5
  - Tufts Journal, March, 2006; UP054.001.011.00020 (Box 11)
    27, 6
  - Tufts Journal, April, 2006; UP054.001.011.00021 (Box 11)
    27, 7
  - Tufts Journal, May, 2006; UP054.001.011.00022 (Box 11)
    27, 8